A Guide to the The Edgar Cayce Readings, 1886-2020
The Edgar Cayce Foundation
- Source file, Collection of secondary sources related to individual readings created by Gladys Davis Turner, Charles Sinex and the E.C.F. staff in the mid-1970s.
  - Box 297
    - biographical information [James Windsor], Folder 297:14
    - biographical information [general], Folder 297:15; -Kenneth Drummond -Laura Kathryn Anderson -Ronald Stewart Jacobson -Christine Morrissey George -Lyttleton Ballard -Richard O'Connor -Gladys Davis Turner -Rabbi Herbert Weiner -Jim and Phyllis Embleton -A.R.E. staff
    - obituaries, Folder 297:16; -Wilfred Sechrist -Elsie Sechrist -Gregory Cayce -Hugh Lynn Cayce -Albert Turner -Gladys Davis Turner -Thomas Sugrue -Violet Shelley -Egerton Sykes -Charlotte Schoen -Harold Reilly -Shane Miller -Roberta Caryer -Henry Miller -Lillia F. Elder -Noah Miller -Nellie Eaton -Ruth LeNoir -Mary W. Kane -David Kahn -Wesley Ketchum -Bryant Reeve -Mary LaPrelle Stevens -Douglas T. Johnston -J. Everett Irion -Sarah Cayce Hesson -Joan Grant -Helen Godfrey -Arthur Marsden Godfrey -Jeffrey Furst -William H. Eigen -Joseph Dunn -Julia Chandler -Gina Cerminara -Sally Taylor Cayce -Edgar Cayce -Ruth M. Braun -Peter Ballbusch -Juliet Brooke Ballard -Lester Babcoke -Les Wilmore -Thomas Burr House -Jess Stearn -Joseph A. Schwartz -Meredith Ann Puryear -Ahmed A. Fayed -Mae Gimbert St. Clair -Cynthia Wallace Butler -Mary Blumenthal Kane -Hazel L. Andersen -Nell Clairmonte -Kieth VonderOhe -Shirley Rabb Winston -Alan Martin Smith -Ann Lee Clapp -Paul V. Haenni, Jr. -Ian Stevenson
    - perpetual motion machine, Folder 297:17-297:18
    - Pit table game, Folder 297:19
  - Box 298
    - San Saba oil drilling, Folder 298:1
    - Still-Hildreth Sanatorium, Folder 298:2
    - well on Cayce Hospital property, Folder 298:3
    - 304 [asthma], Folder 298:4
    - 308 [worms], Folder 298:5
    - 311 [diet], Folder 298:6
    - 311 [Rosicrucianism], Folder 298:7
    - 341 [Project X], Folder 298:8
    - 528 [schleroderma], Folder 298:9
    - 3109 [allergies], Folder 298:10
    - 3117 [children], Folder 298:11
    - 3124 [multiple sclerosis], Folder 298:12
    - 3265 [tic douloureux], Folder 298:13
    - 3268 [sprue], Folder 298:14
    - 3480 [catarrh], Folder 298:15
    - 3511 [deafness], Folder 298:16
    - 3511 [head noises], Folder 298:17
    - 3562 [hydrocephalus], Folder 298:18
    - 3587 [Paget's disease], Folder 298:19
    - 3597 [undulant fever], Folder 298:20
    - 3658 [fistula], Folder 298:21
    - 3681 [muscular dystrophy], Folder 298:22
    - 3997 [pineal gland], Folder 298:23
  - Box 299
    - chronology of the life and work of Edgar Cayce, undated; Folder 299:1
    - correspondence and research materials [Bowling Green and Hopkinsville, Kentucky] D.D. Cayce, 1975-2014; Folder 299:2-299:3
    - essay [Edgar Cayce and the Crucial Years: Texas and Dayton, 1919-1925] Robert W. Krajenke, 2008; Folder 299:4
    - research materials [Dayton, Ohio], 2005-2010; Folder 299:5
    - trial transcripts [Detroit and New York City cases], 1931-1935; Folder 299:6